{
    "subject": "resource/Joey_Molland",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedBand",
    "object": "resource/Natural_Gas_(band)",
    "human_readable": "Joey Molland was associated with the band Natural Gas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9427734017372131,
            "question": "What band was Joey Molland associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8575039505958557,
            "question": "Name a band that Joey Molland was part of."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7738462090492249,
            "question": "Was Joey Molland a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.730038046836853,
            "question": "What other bands or musicians were associated with Natural Gas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7221513390541077,
            "question": "Who is Joey Molland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.562221109867096,
            "question": "When was Joey Molland active in the music industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3923262059688568,
            "question": "What genre of music was Natural Gas known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30198153853416443,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Joey Molland's musical career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2587398290634155,
            "question": "Does Joey Molland have any solo work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11648184806108475,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Natural Gas's popularity?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joey Molland was associated with the band Natural Gas.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8545_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Joey Molland have any solo work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8545_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Joey Molland's musical career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8545_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music was Natural Gas known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8545_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8545_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8545_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8545_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8545_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8545_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8545_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8545_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8545_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8545_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8545_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8545/re-ranker-msmarco/71.txt, it is mentioned that Joey Molland was associated with the band Natural Gas.\n* This association is also confirmed in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8545/re-ranker-msmarco/56.txt.\n\nTherefore, based on the provided context information, I conclude that:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Joey Molland's musical career, including his association with Badfinger and later with the short-lived band Natural Gas. Specifically, the document at path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8545/re-ranker-msmarco/71.txt` mentions that Joey Molland was involved in forming the band Natural Gas alongside Mark Clarke and other musicians."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}